Guide to the News Service subject files, 1930-ongoing
Duke University. University Archives
- Container List
  - Duke/Durham, 1998 (Box 95)
  - Duke, James Buchanan, Pre-1980 only (Box 95)
  - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 95)
  - Angier Biddle Duke, 1972- (Box 95)
  - Duke, Doris, 1993 (Box 95)
  - Duke, Doris (Box 95)
  - Duke Family, 1987 (Box 95)
  - Duke Family, 1988- (Box 95)
  - Duke, Washington (Box 95)
  - Duke Acoustic Center (Box 95)
  - Duke Award permanent file (Box 95)
  - Duke Award, 1987-1989 (Box 95)
  - Duke Campus Ministry (Box 95)
  - Duke Campus Ministry, 1987 (Box 95)
  - Duke Campus Ministry, 1988 (Box 95)
  - Duke- Civic Center, 1981 (Box 95)
  - Duke Endowment, 1994-1995 (Box 95)
  - Duke Family, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Duke Homestead, 1975 (Box 95)
  - Duke Homestead, 1977 (Box 95)
  - Duke University, General, 1986 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1987 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1988 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1989 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1990 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1991 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1992 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1993 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1994 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1995-1996 (Box 96)
  - Duke University, General, 1997-1998 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1987 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1988 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1989 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1990 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1991 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1994 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1975 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, January 1977 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1981 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1978-1979 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1992-1993 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1995 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest, 1996 (Box 96)
  - Duke Forest (Box 96)
  - Duke University General, 1978 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1979 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1980 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1981 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1981 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1981 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1981 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1983 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1983 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1984 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1985 (Box 97)
  - Duke University General, 1985 (Box 97)
  - Duke in the News, 1985 (Box 97)
  - Duke in the News, 1986 (Box 97)
  - Duke in the News (Box 97)
  - New York Times and National Magazine Clippings (Box 97)
  - Foreign Clippings (Box 97)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1989 (Box 97)
  - Durham County Centenial, 1981 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1983 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1984 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1985 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1986 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1987 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press 1988 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1989 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1993 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1994 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Press, 1995 (Box 98)
  - Duke, James Buchanan (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1975-1977 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1978-1981 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1982-1986 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1987 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1988 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1990 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1991 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 1992 (Box 98)
  - Duke University Historical Data 1997-1999 (Box 98)
  - Duke University General, 1977 (Box 98)
  - Trustees, Duke Endowment (Box 98)
  - Education, 1991- (Box 99)
  - Education Improvement Programs, 1975- (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1977 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1978 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1979 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1980 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1981 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1983 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1984 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1985 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1986 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1987 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1988 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1990 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Editorials includes Letters to the Editor, 1992 (Box 99)
  - Editorials, 1995 (Box 99)
  - Economics, 1966 (Box 99)
  - Economics, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Economics, 1991 (Box 99)
  - Eastward, 1977 (Box 99)
  - Crain/ Mahard Desegregation (Box 99)
  - Education, 1980-1982 (Box 99)
  - Education, 1983-1984 (Box 99)
  - Education, 1985 (Box 99)
  - Education, 1975 (Box 99)
  - Education, 1986 (Box 99)
  - Education, 1987-1988 (Box 99)
  - Education, current file (Box 99)
  - Education, 1989 (Box 99)
  - Education, 1990 (Box 99)
  - Engineering, 1976 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1977 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1978 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1979 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1980 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1981 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1983 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1984 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, General and Duke, 1975-1984 (Box 100)
  - Employees, General, 1988 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, (General and Duke) (Box 100)
  - Endowment, General, 1991 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, Duke, 1991 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, Duke, 1990 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, 1987 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, Duke (Box 100)
  - Endowment, Duke, 1989 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, General, 1990 (Box 100)
  - Endowment, General (Box 100)
  - Employees, General (Box 100)
  - Employee Relations, 1988 (Box 100)
  - Employee Relations, 1975- (Box 100)
  - Employee Relations, 1989 (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Employee Relations, 1990- (Box 100)
  - Employee Training, 1988 (Box 100)
  - Employee Training (Box 100)
  - Employee Benefits, 1992 (Box 100)
  - Employee Benefits, 1982 (Box 100)
  - Employee Benefits, 1988 (Box 100)
  - Employee Benefits, 1989-1990 (Box 100)
  - Employee Benefits, 1991(2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Employees, General, 1996 (Box 100)
  - Employees, General, 1987 (Box 100)
  - Employees, General (2 folders) (Box 100)
  - Employees, General, 1990 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1994 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1991- (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1990 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1989 (Box 100)
  - Engineering (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1987 (Box 100)
  - Engineering, 1986 (Box 100)
  - English, 1995-1996 (Box 101)
  - English, 1975 (Box 101)
  - English Department, 1982 (Box 101)
  - English Department, 1985 (Box 101)
  - English Department, 1988 (Box 101)
  - English Department, 1989 (Box 101)
  - English Department, 1990 (Box 101)
  - English Department, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits (Art, Photos), 1985 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits, 1987 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits, 1988 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits, 1989 (Box 101)
  - Exhibits, 1990 (Box 101)
  - Environmental Health Center (Box 101)
  - Enrollment, 1987 (Box 101)
  - Enrollment, 1988 (Box 101)
  - Enrollment, 1989 (Box 101)
  - Enrollment, 1990 (Box 101)
  - Enrollment, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Enrollment (Box 101)
  - Faculty Clippings, 1975-1980 (Box 101)
  - Faculty Appointments and Promotions, 1977 (Box 101)
  - Faculty (General), 1981-1984 (Box 101)
  - Faculty (General), 1985 (Box 101)
  - Faculty Appointments and Promotions, 1987 (Box 101)
  - Faculty Appointments and Promotions, 1988 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff, General, 1990 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff, General, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff Appointment and Promotions, 1988 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff Appointment and Promotions, 1989 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff Appointment and Promotions, 1990 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff Appointment and Promotions, 1991 (Box 101)
  - Faculty and Staff (General) (2 folders) (Box 101)
  - Faculty Club, 1961- (Box 102)
  - Faculty Club, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Faculty In-Residence (2 folders) (Box 102)
  - Faculty Newsletter, 1984- (Box 102)
  - Fellowships - National Association of Science Writers (Box 102)
  - Fellowships, 1975 (Box 102)
  - Fellowships, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Fellowships, 1989-1990 (Box 102)
  - Fellowships, Presidential, 1989-1990 (Box 102)
  - Festivals (Moroccan and others), 1985 (Box 102)
  - Film, 1975 (Box 102)
  - Films/Filmed on Campus, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Film and Video Program, 1994 (Box 102)
  - Financial Aid - Students, 1982 (Box 102)
  - Financial Aid, 1987 (Box 102)
  - Finacial Aid, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Financial Aid, 1989-1990 (Box 102)
  - Financial Aid, 1991 (Box 102)
  - Financial Aid, 1992 (Box 102)
  - First Fifty Years: Milestones on a Long Journey, 1975 (Box 102)
  - Flentrop Organ, 1976-1979 (Box 102)
  - Flentrop Organ, 1985 (Box 102)
  - Flentrop Organ, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Folk Festival, 1975- (Box 102)
  - Foreign Clippings, [1982-1983] (Box 102)
  - Foreign Students, 1970- (Box 102)
  - Forest History Society, 1984- (Box 102)
  - Forest History Society, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Forestry, 1987 (Box 102)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1989-1990 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1979 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1980 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1981 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1982 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1983 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1984 (Box 102)
  - Forestry School, 1985 (Box 102)
  - Former Employees (Box 102)
  - Former Employees, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Former Employees, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Former Employees, 1990 (Box 102)
  - Former Employees, 1991 (Box 102)
  - Former Employees, 1992 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, 1975 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day Convocation (Box 102)
  - Founders Society, 1980 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1987 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1988 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1989 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1990 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1991 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1992 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1993 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1994 (Box 102)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society, 1995 (Box 102)
  - Business Admin. from 1976 (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1979 (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1980 (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1981 (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1982 (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1983 (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1984 (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1985 (2 folders) (Box 103)
  - Business School, 1986 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1989 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1991 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1993 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1994 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Fraternities, 1975 (Box 103)
  - French (Box 103)
  - Freshman and Freshman Activities, 1991 (Box 103)
  - Freshman Activities, 1975 (Box 103)
  - Freshman Advisory Program, 1975 (Box 103)
  - Freshman and Freshman Activities, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Freshman and Freshman Activities, 1989 (Box 103)
  - Freshman and Freshman Activities, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Freshman and Freshman Activities, 1993, 1994, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Freshmen and Freshmen Activities, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Fritz London Memorial Fund, 1973 (Box 103)
  - Functions at Duke not Related to Duke, 1987 (Box 103)
  - Functions at Duke not Related to Duke, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Functions at Duke not Related to Duke, 1989 (Box 103)
  - Functions at Duke not Related to Duke, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Functions at Duke not Related to Duke, 1991 (Box 103)
  - Functions on Duke Campus (Not Duke-related), 1980 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1986 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1987 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1989 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1990 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1991 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1992 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1993 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1994 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1995 (Box 103)
  - Fundraising, 1996 (Box 103)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1988 (Box 103)
  - Duke Gardens, 1975 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1989 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1990 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1991 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1992 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1995 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1996 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 1998 (Box 104)
  - Fuqua, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, 1996 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, 1998 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1987 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1988 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1989 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1990 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1991 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1993 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1994 (Box 104)
  - Gardens, Duke, 1995 (Box 104)
  - Gender Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 105)
  - Geology, 1975 (Box 105)
  - Geology, 1989 (Box 105)
  - Geology, 1990 (Box 105)
  - Germanic Languages and Lit., 1991 (Box 105)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature, 1976, 1977, 1985 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1986-1987 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1988 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1989 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1990 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1991 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1993 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1994-1995 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1996 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, 1998 (Box 105)
  - Gifts, Miscellaneous (other than grants), 1977-1985 (Box 105)
  - Golf Tournament, 1975-1984 (Box 105)
  - Golf Tournament, 1985 (Box 105)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1977 (Box 105)
  - Graduate School, 1989-1990 (Box 105)
  - Graduate School, 1991-1996 (Box 105)
  - Grants, 1975-1984 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1977-1984 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1985 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1987 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1988 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1989 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1990 (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1991 (2 folders) (Box 106)
  - Grants, 1993-1998 (Box 106)
  - Gubernatorial Fellows Program, 1985- (Box 106)
  - Hats Off (Box 106)
  - Health and Safety, 1989 (Box 106)
  - Health and Safety, 1990 (Box 106)
  - Health Fair, 1975 - (Box 106)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1978-1984 (Box 106)
  - History Dept., 1987- (Box 106)
  - History, 1977-1986 (Box 106)
  - History, 1989-1990 (Box 106)
  - History, 1991- (Box 106)
  - History, 1993 (Box 106)
  - History, 1994 (Box 106)
  - History, 1995 (Box 106)
  - History, 1996 (Box 106)
  - Academic Council, 1991- (Box 107)
  - Admissions, 1999-2000 (Box 107)
  - African-American Studies, 1990-2000 (Box 107)
  - Alumni/Alumni Affairs, 2000-2001 (Box 107)
  - American Dance Festival, 1997-2002 (Box 107)
  - Annual Fund, 1989- (Box 107)
  - Art and Art History, 2000- (Box 107)
  - Art Museum, 2001-2002 (Box 107)
  - Artist Series, 1993- (Box 107)
  - Artist-In-Residence, 1991 (Box 107)
  - Asian and African Languages, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Asian Pacific Studies, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Athletics at Duke, 1997-2001 (Box 107)
  - Auxiliary-Duke Hospital, 1991 (Box 107)
  - Awards, 1997- (Box 107)
  - Biological Anthropology and Anatomy, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Biology, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Biomedical Engineering, 1993- (Box 107)
  - Botany, 1994 - (Box 107)
  - Budget and Finance, 1997- (Box 107)
  - Buildings and Grounds, 1997- (Box 107)
  - Cable 13, 1991- (Box 107)
  - Campus Ministry, 1991- (Box 107)
  - Canadian Studies, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Capital Campaign for Arts and Sciences, 1993- (Box 107)
  - Career Development Center, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Center for Demographic Studies, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Center for Documentary Studies, 2000 (Box 107)
  - Center for East-West Trade, Investments, and Communication, 1994 (Box 107)
  - Center for European Studies, 1993- (Box 107)
  - Center for Health Policy Research and Education, 1991- (Box 107)
  - Center for International Development and Research, 1989- (Box 107)
  - Center for International Studies, 1996-2001 (Box 107)
  - Center for Jewish Life, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Center for Living (Box 107)
  - Center for Slavic, Eurasian, and East European Studies, 1994- (Box 107)
  - Center for the Study of Aging and Human Development, 1997- (Box 107)
  - Center for the Study of Communications and Journalism, 2000- (Box 107)
  - Center for the Study of Congress (Box 107)
  - Center for the Study of Philanthropy and Volunteerism, 1991 (Box 107)
  - Child Protection, Center for (Box 107)
  - Children's Classic, 2000- (Box 107)
  - Center for Teaching and Learning, 1993- (Box 108)
  - Chamber Arts Society, 1992- (Box 108)
  - Chapel, Duke, 2000-, 2001 (Box 108)
  - Chemistry, 2000- (Box 108)
  - Chronicle, 1999- (Box 108)
  - Ciompi Quartet, 1997 (Box 108)
  - Classical Studies, 1991-, 1994 - (Box 108)
  - Commencement, 2000-2002 (Box 108)
  - Community Service Center (Box 108)
  - Computer Science, 2000- (Box 108)
  - Conferences and Seminars, 1999- (Box 108)
  - Continuing Education, 2000-2001 (Box 108)
  - Cook (Samuel DuBois) Society (Box 108)
  - Counseling and Psychological Services (CAPS), 1991- (Box 108)
  - Craft Center, 1993- (Box 108)
  - Credit Union, 1991- (Box 108)
  - Ctr. for World Environment and Sustainable Development, 1992- (Box 108)
  - Cultural Affairs, 1994- (Box 108)
  - Cultural Anthropology, 1995- (Box 108)
  - Curriculum, 1999- (Box 108)
  - Dance Program, 1995- (Box 108)
  - Day Care Center, 1991- (Box 108)
  - Dean's List, 1991- (Box 108)
  - Development, 1997- (Box 108)
  - Dining Halls, 1994- (Box 108)
  - Distinguished Professorships, 1994- (Box 108)
  - Distinguished Teaching Awards, 1992- (Box 108)
  - Divinity, 2000-2001 (Box 108)
  - Doris Duke Charitable Foundation (Box 108)
  - Drama Program, 1998- (Box 108)
  - Drugs (Abuse, Prevention), 2001-2002 (Box 108)
  - Duke Award (for N.C. Press Association only), 1990- (Box 108)
  - Duke Education Program (Box 108)
  - Duke Endowment, 1998- (Box 108)
  - Duke Family, 1993- (Box 108)
  - Duke Forest, 1999 (Box 108)
  - Duke Golf Course (Box 108)
  - Duke University Historical Data, 2001- (Box 108)
  - Duke University Press, 1997-2000 (Box 108)
  - Duke University, General, 1997-1998, 2000- (Box 108)
  - Duke, Angier Biddle (Box 108)
  - Duke, Anthony Drexel (Box 108)
  - Duke, Benjamin Newton (Box 108)
  - Duke, Doris, 1997- (Box 108)
  - Duke, George St. George Biddle (Box 108)
  - Duke, James. B., 1994- (Box 108)
  - Duke, Washington, 1993- (Box 108)
  - Duke/Durham, 2000 (Box 109)
  - Durham Regional Hospital, 2000- (Box 109)
  - Economics, 1997- (Box 109)
  - Editorials/Letters, 2001 (Box 109)
  - Education, 1993- (Box 109)
  - Employee Benefits, 1999-2000 (Box 109)
  - Employee Relations (Box 109)
  - Employee Training, 1989 - (Box 109)
  - Employee, General, 1995-2000 (Box 109)
  - Endowment, 1997- (Box 109)
  - Engineering, 2000- (Box 109)
  - English, 1999-2002 (Box 109)
  - Enrollment, 1996- (Box 109)
  - Facilities and Planning, 1999- (Box 109)
  - Faculty and Staff, General, 1999-2002 (Box 109)
  - Faculty Appointments and Promotions, 2000 (Box 109)
  - Faculty Club, 1989- (Box 109)
  - Film and Video Program, 1995- (Box 109)
  - Films/Filmed on Campus, 1999- (Box 109)
  - Financial Aid, 1999- (Box 109)
  - Former Employees, 1997- (Box 109)
  - Founders' Day, Founders' Society (Box 109)
  - Franklin Center (Box 109)
  - Fraternities and Sororities, 1997- (Box 109)
  - Free Electron Laser, 1994- (Box 109)
  - Freshman Advisory Board, 1989- (Box 109)
  - Freshman and Freshman Activities, 1997- (Box 109)
  - Functions at Duke not related to Duke, 1992- (Box 109)
  - Fundraising, 1999-2000 (Box 109)
  - Fuqua School of Business, 2001-2002 (Box 109)
  - Gardens, Duke, 2001 (Box 109)
  - Gay Assn. (Box 109)
  - Gender Relations, 1999- (Box 109)
  - Genome Sciences and Policy, Institute for (Box 109)
  - Geology, 1991- (Box 109)
  - Germanic Languages and Literature, 1994- (Box 109)
  - Gifts, 2001 (Box 109)
  - Governors Center, 1993- (Box 109)
  - Grants, 1997- (Box 109)
  - Department of Medicine, 1997- (Box 110)
  - Graduate School, 1995- (Box 110)
  - Health and Safety, 1991- (Box 110)
  - Health, Physical Education and Recreation, 1991- (Box 110)
  - History, 1998-1999 (Box 110)
  - Honorary Degree Recipients, 1998-1999 (Box 110)
  - Hoof 'n' Horn, 1989- (Box 110)
  - Housing, 1999- (Box 110)
  - Human Resources, 1997- (Box 110)
  - Information Systems, 1990- (Box 110)
  - Institute for Learning in Retirement, 1994- (Box 110)
  - Institute for the Human Agenda, 1989- (Box 110)
  - Institute of Statistics and Decision Sciences, 1989- (Box 110)
  - Institute of the Arts, 1996- (Box 110)
  - International Affairs, 1998- (Box 110)
  - International House, 1991- (Box 110)
  - International Studies Program, 1994- (Box 110)
  - Internship Programs, 1993- (Box 110)
  - Investments and Real Estate, 1991- (Box 110)
  - Islamic and Arabian Studies, 1989- (Box 110)
  - Jazz, 1994- (Box 110)
  - Judaic Studies, 1991- (Box 110)
  - Kenan Ethics Program (Box 110)
  - Latin American Studies Program, 1994- (Box 110)
  - Law School, 2001-2002 (Box 110)
  - Lectures and Speakers, 2001- (Box 110)
  - Legal Action against Duke, 1997- (Box 110)
  - Levine Science Research Center, 1992- (Box 110)
  - Liberal Studies - MA Program, 1991- (Box 110)
  - Major Speakers, 2001- (Box 110)
  - Marine Laboratory, 1997- (Box 110)
  - Martin Luther King Celebration/Commemoration, 1992-, 1995- (Box 110)
  - Mary Lou Williams Center and Jazz Festival, 1992-, 1995- (Box 110)
  - Mathematics, 1991- (Box 110)
  - Medical Center Alumni Association, 1992 (Box 110)
  - Medical Center, General, 2001-2002 (Box 110)
  - Medieval and Renaissance Studies, 1989- (Box 110)
  - Microelectronics, 1990- (Box 110)
  - Minority Affairs, 2001- (Box 110)
  - Music, 1998- (Box 110)
  - National Humanities Center, 1989- (Box 110)
  - News Service, Duke (Box 110)
  - North American Studies Center (Box 110)
  - Nursing, School of, 1991- (Box 110)
  - North Carolina Press Association, 1994- (Box 111)
  - Office of Science and Technology, 1993- (Box 111)
  - Office of University Life, 1993- (Box 111)
  - Partnership for Literacy, 1993- (Box 111)
  - Perkins Library System (Box 111)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1991- (Box 111)
  - Philosophy, 1991- (Box 111)
  - Photography, University (Box 111)
  - Physics, 2001- (Box 111)
  - Phytotron, 1991- (Box 111)
  - Policies and Regulations, 1998- (Box 111)
  - Political Science, 1998- (Box 111)
  - President's Research Fellowships (Box 111)
  - Primate Center, 1998- (Box 111)
  - Professorships, James B. Duke, 1989- (Box 111)
  - Program in Literature, 1993- (Box 111)
  - Psychology (Box 111)
  - Public Safety/Crime, 2001- (Box 111)
  - Publications (Journals, Magazines Pub. by Duke), 1992- (Box 111)
  - Radio Station WXDU, 1989- (Box 111)
  - Rankings, 1997-1998, 2000-2002 (Box 111)
  - Religion, 1997- (Box 111)
  - Religious Activities - Students, 1996- (Box 111)
  - Research Studies (Medical), 1997- (Box 111)
  - Research Studies (University), 1994- (Box 111)
  - Research Triangle Institute, 1990- (Box 111)
  - Rhodes Scholars from Duke, 1991- (Box 111)
  - Rice Diet, 1995- (Box 111)
  - Romance Languages and Literature, 1995- (Box 111)
  - ROTC, 1992 (Box 111)
  - Roundtable on Science and Public Affairs, 1989- (Box 111)
  - Savoyards, 1990- (Box 111)
  - Scholarships (B.N. Duke), 1990- (Box 111)
  - Scholarships, General, 2001- (Box 111)
  - Scholarships, Individual, 1990- (Box 111)
  - School of the Environment, 2001- (2 subfolders) (Box 111)
  - Science, 1992- (Box 111)
  - Science, Technology and Human Values, 1991- (Box 111)
  - Sexual Harassment/Policy, 1993-, 1995- (Box 111)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature, 1991- (Box 111)
  - Sociology, 1994- (Box 111)
  - Students, General, 2001-2002 (Box 111)
  - Acoustic Center, 1991 (Box 112)
  - AIDS Research, 2000- (Box 112)
  - Allergy Center, 1991 (Box 112)
  - Alzheimer's Disease, 2000- (Box 112)
  - Anesthesiology, 1991- (Box 112)
  - Animal Research, 1992- (Box 112)
  - Arthritis Center, 1992- (Box 112)
  - Behavioral Research Center, 1991- (Box 112)